foxhead.com 2015-09-05

# Privacy Policy | Fox Racing - Foxhead.com

Fox Head, Inc. respects the privacy of every individual who visits our websites. This Privacy Policy outlines the information Fox Head, Inc. may collect and how we may use that information.

PERSONAL DATA

Fox Head, Inc. will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you (e.g., your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address ("personal data") through our websites unless you have provided it to us voluntarily. If you do not want your personal data collected, please do not submit it to us.

When you do provide us with personal data, we may use that information in the following ways, unless stated otherwise: we may store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services; we (or a fulfillment house or other third party on our behalf in connection with a promotion)may use that information to contact you; and/or we may provide other third parties with aggregate - but not individual - information about visitors to or users of our sites. We do not now and do not intend to sell, rent or market personal data about you to third parties.

CHILDREN

Fox Head, Inc. has no intention of collecting any personal data from individuals under thirteen years of age. Where appropriate, the Company will specifically instruct children not to submit such information on our websites and/or will take reasonable steps to ensure parental consent to such submission.

Parents should be aware that Fox Head, Inc.'s Privacy Policy will govern our use of personal data, but that information which is voluntarily given by children -- or others -- in chat sessions, e-mail exchanges, bulletin boards or the like may be used by other parties to generate unsolicited mail. Fox Head encourages all parents to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their personal data while using the Internet.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED AUTOMATICALLY

In some cases, we may automatically (i.e., not via registration) collect technical information when you connect to our site that is not personally-identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet Browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site.

INFORMATION PLACED AUTOMATICALLY ON YOUR COMPUTER -- COOKIES

When you view one of our websites, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "Cookie" or similar file and can help us in many ways. For example, Cookies allow us to tailor a website to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.
